#### **Personal Information**

Last name: Zunzunwala First name: Apurva

Address: schweidnitzer Strasse 3, 10709,

Berlin

Telefon: +49 151 45095486

Email: apu.zunzunwala@gmail.com

Year of Birth: 1989



Github profile: <a href="https://github.com/ApurvaZun">https://github.com/ApurvaZun</a>

LinkedIn profile: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/apurva-zunzunwala-b31681120/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/apurva-zunzunwala-b31681120/</a>

# Languages

English: Business Fluent

Hindi: Native German: A1.1

# **Summary**

I have held responsible positions in a number of companies specialising in IT services as a programmer. My practical experience includes working in **Frontend Development for more than 2 years** and Database development for 6 years. I am looking for a company willing to offer me a placement among their developers. In return, I would offer my full commitment, and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team.

### **Experience**

### Repay.Me, Berlin Frontend Developer

tend Developer 3rd Sep 2018 – 15th Jan 2020

- Develop the frontend of the ecommerce website in collaboration with UX designer.
- Extensive use of ISML which is wrapper over HTML, pipelines, webforms and CMS in intershop.
- Help the team take key decisions in technical designs and implementations in frontend area.
- Strong use of **JQuery** and Javascript libraries like bootstrap validator, date picker etc.
- Programming in React.js to develop application which has search engine using Bing API, Auth0 authentication.
- Writing Functional and Class Components, Controlled Forms, hooks.
- Developing of SPA and UI components with React.
- Experience in using CSS/LESS, grids, performance optimisation.

- Web Responsive Coding and Asynchronous Programming.
- Wide use of various API and plugins for various modules like Facebook login, QR code, Ad detection, Data analytics tool etc.
- Involved in Code Reviews, Grooming and Retrospective.

# Accenture, Latvia

**Application Developer** 

9th Oct 2017 - 9th Mar 2018

#### Oracle Cloud Financials ERP (Fusion and SOA) for Auchan

- Customization of Oracle Cloud Finance and Accounting applications for Auchan present in 14 countries.
- I was involved in automation of loading files (e.g. PO, Suppliers, Auto Invoices etc) from Third Party through SOAP Webservices available in Oracle Fusion Application R13.
- I was involved in the Integration Team which was responsible to load and extract data in Cloud Application through SOA. I was also part of defining BPEL processes to consume webservices to extract and upload data in application.
- Testing Webservices using SOAPUI and writing Interface Documents for Fusion Application.
- Playing Business Integration Publisher Role to generate Customized Reports for Clients.

#### **Deutsche Bank, Pune**

Senior Analyst

17th Oct 2016 - 30th Mar 2017

# DBAART, a regulatory reporting for banking domain

- I was part of a team whose primary responsibility was to generate regulatory reports for India, US, Malaysia, Singapore, Thailand using the proprietary banking tool Axiom.
- I was also involved in transaction data warehousing and data loading.
- I used to create low level design documentation and consume new requirements from Business Analyst.
- Development and Code deployment in different environment

#### Cognizant, Pune

Senior Developer

 $21^{st}$  May  $2014 - 27^{th}$  Sep 2016

#### Unsecured IVR, a payment service for collection & recovery of loans for Lloyds bank

- Writing low level design documents for development purpose.
- Attending high level design calls for environment setup and design queries.
- Writing Unix shell scripts to load the data in staging table.
- Writing Unix shell scripts to load data in work tables.
- Providing support to QA team at the time of Migration event.
- Fixing bugs and giving solution in minimum time at the time of events.

### Loan Heritage Migration, a data migration system for loans for Lloyds bank

- Writing plsql code for the migration of Loans data(Collection and Recovery) from legacy system.
- Writing scripts to load the data in staging table.

- Writing Sql Loader scripts to load data in work tables.
- Writing Plsql code to build reports.
- Doing performance tuning.
- Providing support to QA team at the time of Migration event.

#### System of Reference & CI migration, an ETL process for KPN client

- Doing development that includes: shell scripts, control files, packages, triggers, procedures, functions.
- Creating new data model for data migration activity.
- Data Migration activity: creating new table structure and loading data and Creating indexes
- Basic working knowledge of Pentaho.
- Ensured to deliver defect and bug free code by doing rigorous testing.
- SIT/ACC/PROD deployment and testing.
- Providing support to testing team.
- Resolving production incidents within SLA.

#### Tech Mahindra, Pune

Software Engineer

24th July 2011 - 9th May 2014

# Provide IP/PIP Development, an order management system for British Telecom

- I received training for 3 months in HTML, CSS, javascript, plsql, unix.
- Requirement Analysis with respect to the impact in terms of functionality and development.
- Delivering the requirements in the targeted time.
- Providing Support (resolutions to queries, resolving issues etc) to ASG (2<sup>nd</sup> Line Support).
- Providing support to testing teams like resolving their queries, fixing bugs/defects quickly.
- Deal with Service Requests, Ad-hoc requests/Queries
- I had an E2E understanding of the system, interacted with component delivery teams, Delivery Managers, Solution Designers, testers with a view to understand the system.
- Involved in developing and maintaining application using vanilla javascript and html, plsql, unix scripting.

# **Education**

Bachelor in Computer Science, Nagpur University, India June 2008 - May 2011

High School -J.B Science College, Maharashtra, India June 2006 - April 2008

# Skills

**Programming Skills:** 

HTML, ISML CSS, Less, SASS Javascript, ES6 JQuery React.js Redux Webpack docker Microsoft Azure Git npm Oracle database

Operating System Windows Mac OS Linux

# **Certificates/Training:**

- Web Development Bootcamp from Udemy.
  Certificate URL <a href="https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-RXMRWVPW/">https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-RXMRWVPW/</a>
  Oracle SOA 12c Certified Implementation Specialist
- Oracle SOA 12c Certified Implementation Specialist Certificate URL - <a href="https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/91861696-4437-4770-8db9-e4f3ea3e4fca/linked\_in\_profile">https://www.youracclaim.com/badges/91861696-4437-4770-8db9-e4f3ea3e4fca/linked\_in\_profile</a>

# **Hobbies:**

I love dancing.